textadventures.co.uk 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy - textadventures.co.uk

## Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or date of birth. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used:

  * to show games that are appropriate for your age
  * to contact you with information about your account

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. We use cookies to allow you stay logged in to the site, so you don't have to re-enter your login details.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us.
